[{"answer": "So you gonna abide by the court's ruling or you gonna go Bandi", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I guess if you really wanted to hang out in from of a convenience store, you could just buy your own no", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "When you're right, you're right. I wish I'd broken off a little piece for myself. Because if the buzz is any indication, the movie's gonna make some huge bank", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The Internet buzz", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's a thre", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place's in that place, sir", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You gotta induce the drivers a little", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Like this", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, but we ain't gay", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, I don't wanna cough up some dude's sperm", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "All hitchers do this. Why do you think people pick us up? If you get a ride, it's expecte", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The unwritten Book of the that place", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So where are you boys from", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What brings you to that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "We're going to that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That's good to hear. But it takes deed, not words. It's a lot easier to say you live by the Book than to actually do it.  Can you do it", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No time like the present, right", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Even sheep", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They are beautiful, aren't they", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You can't exclude an animal just because it's not cuddly. Of course I like snakes", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What's a trouser snake", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We'll find someone else. Besides, I didn't see you trying to stop my friend from throwing him out", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Cover, shmove", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We don't have a jet, sir. And that place's only ten minutes away", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, if it isn't the wildlife experts. Did you come to it or go to it", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We have a toaster oven. Why", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hey, shove it. Bounc", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "O", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No it ain't all good. Oh, you think I want it now, after your lips touched the cup? Get the fuck off my set", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No you the Man! And that's the problem", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Look at this shit.  A gay hood ornament, and the color Purple", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Who the fuck am I? I'm the fucking director, is who I am. Chaka Luther King. The creator of all of this", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "And they're not the leaders of C.L.I.T. The C.L.I.T. is not real", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Are you guys alright", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'll explain later, my friend  In exchange, I'll give you the diamonds I stole, and turn in Sissy, my friend, my friend, and myself. But I want a reduced sentence", "docId": "Jay-and-Silent-Bob-Strike-Back.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " For him? I'd be willing to do anything", "qsentId": 38}]